xcellhost.in 2014-07-03

# XcellHost Cloud Services Pvt. Ltd. > About Us > Legal Info > Policies > Privacy Policy

### I. What information does XcellHost Cloud Services Pvt. Ltd. collect and how is it used?

There are a variety of situations in which XcellHost Cloud Services Pvt. Ltd. may collect personal information, such as when you register as a customer; purchase one of our products/ services; download case studies or white papers; order email newsletters; respond to a marketing campaign; place orders on our website; or when you’re working with a XcellHost Cloud Services Pvt. Ltd. service representative. In each of those situations, XcellHost Cloud Services Pvt. Ltd. only collects the personal information required to meet your needs. Depending on the circumstances, we may ask for your name, company name, Internet domain name, industry, IP address, billing or shipping address, credit card information, email address, fax number, phone number, or other pertinent information. XcellHost Cloud Services Pvt. Ltd. uses your information to better understand your needs, provide you with the services you have requested, and with a view to provide you with better service. We may use your information to help you complete a transaction, (including fulfillment of orders and promotional offers), to communicate back to you, to inform you of service updates as well as to manage and renew your subscription(s).

Credit card numbers are used only for payment processing, maintenance of your subscription, and fraud protection and are not used for other purposes without your permission. XcellHost Cloud Services Pvt. Ltd. will keep your personal information for as long as you are a registered subscriber or user of our service(s) and thereafter, for no longer than is reasonably necessary for internal reporting and reconciliation purposes and to provide you with any feedback or information that you might request or require.

With the consent of our customers, XcellHost Cloud Services Pvt. Ltd. posts customer testimonials on our website, which may contain personally identifiable information, such as the customer's name. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner materially different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by email or via a prominent notice on our website and where necessary we will seek the prior consent of our users.

If at any time you wish to remove your personal information from a XcellHost Cloud Services Pvt. Ltd. website testimonial, please contact service support. 

### II. Does XcellHost Cloud Services Pvt. Ltd. disclose personal information?

In limited circumstances, XcellHost Cloud Services Pvt. Ltd. may need to share your information in order to meet your particular needs. XcellHost Cloud Services Pvt. Ltd. has a number of relationships with vendors with whom we may share your personal information for the purpose of providing a service, fulfilling an order, or meeting your other needs, including the provision of customer support. For example, we use selected vendors for the purpose of providing credit card transaction and check processing services. These vendors verify your purchase information, such as credit card number or checking account number, and authorize your transaction. In doing so, the vendors have access to limited information about users, but they are prohibited from using the information for any other purpose. XcellHost Cloud Services Pvt. Ltd. imposes strict confidentiality obligations on all third-party vendors with whom we share your information. By providing your information to us, you are deemed to consent to the transfer of your information to XcellHost Cloud Services Pvt. Ltd.'s third-party vendors in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.

We may also need to share your personal information with other legal entities within XcellHost Cloud Services Pvt. Ltd.. All such entities adhere to the XcellHost Cloud Services Pvt. Ltd. Privacy Policy. From time to time, XcellHost Cloud Services Pvt. Ltd. may provide personal information to law enforcement authorities or other third parties in response to a subpoena, an official inquiry, or as may be required in the case of national security. XcellHost Cloud Services Pvt. Ltd. will not disclose your personal information to third parties for their own marketing purposes unless you have provided consent.

E-Billing Solutions (EBS) is a third-party vendor providing e-commerce solutions for XcellHost Cloud Services Pvt. Ltd.'s online payment gateway. As a result, XcellHost Cloud Services Pvt. Ltd. shares certain personal information with EBS to complete your transactions. The protection of such information is addressed in EBS's Privacy Statement. XcellHost Cloud Services Pvt. Ltd. disclaims all liability for the data processing activities of its outside vendors.

### III. How does XcellHost Cloud Services Pvt. Ltd. secure personal information?

Access to personal (confidential) information is restricted to authorized personnel only on need –to-know basis only. Our website is regularly tested for security vulnerabilities to ensure all collected information is secure from unauthorized viewing. Personal customer information is protected in transit via HTTPS and SSL security. Credit card information is transmitted with multiple layers of security, including encryption in storage and SSL in transit. For more information, please review the section on disclosure of information above.

### IV. Can you control how your information is used?

Yes. As mentioned above, XcellHost Cloud Services Pvt. Ltd. may use your information to improve the content of our website, products, and services, or to alert you to information we believe might interest you. When you register or make a purchase, we offer you the opportunity to opt into or out of these uses of your information. If you do not choose to opt out initially, you may still block future contact of this type by simply following the unsubscribe instructions that accompany all such communications, or by writing to the address below.

**Marketing Department**  
**XcellHost Cloud Services Pvt. Ltd.**  
209, Laxmi Plaza, Bldg. No. 9,  
Laxmi Industrial Estate, Andheri (W),  
Mumbai - 400053,  
MAHARASHTRA, INDIA

Please note that we do not allow our customers to opt out of content that is essential to the functionality of our products and services, such as communications relating to necessary updates on our services.

### V. What privacy policy applies if you follow a link on XcellHost Cloud Services Pvt. Ltd.'s website?

Our site contains links to other websites. If you follow one of those links, you may be leaving XcellHost Cloud Services Pvt. Ltd.'s website and entering a site not under XcellHost Cloud Services Pvt. Ltd.'s control. XcellHost Cloud Services Pvt. Ltd. does not accept liability for misuse of any information submitted on any site outside its control. We strongly encourage you to read the privacy statements or policies of the linked sites, as their privacy policies may differ from ours.

### VI. Can you review and update the personal information that XcellHost Cloud Services Pvt. Ltd. collects?

Yes. Existing customers can access and update most of the personal information that XcellHost Cloud Services Pvt. Ltd. holds by visiting the Client Login section for our products and service(s) you are using, or by contacting us at the addresses below:

**XcellHost Cloud Services Pvt. Ltd.**  
209, Laxmi Plaza, Bldg. No. 9,  
Laxmi Industrial Estate, Andheri (W),  
Mumbai - 400053,  
MAHARASHTRA, INDIA

### VII. Does XcellHost Cloud Services Pvt. Ltd. keep track of website visitor data?

Like many other companies, XcellHost Cloud Services Pvt. Ltd. uses “cookies” to remember user preferences and maximize performance of our website and services. Additionally, cookies help us to identify returning users so, for example, we don’t need to ask them to enter their email & password on every visit. Any personal information we collect with cookies is not shared with any outside parties.

Please note the information gathered by cookies is necessary to provide certain subscription services. We cannot provide those services to users who do not give their consent to the data processing carried out through cookies or whose browsers are set to reject all cookies.

Cookies may also be used to control the type and/or frequency of ads, promotions, or other marketing messages the customer views. These ads may be placed by third-party advertising companies. Any information the advertising companies collect is non-personal and anonymous.

As is common on the Internet, XcellHost Cloud Services Pvt. Ltd. maintains log files of the traffic that visits our sites. For example, our servers may automatically record the information you or your browser send when you visit a website. These log files may include information such as your requests, IP address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request, and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your system.

### VIII. How often does XcellHost Cloud Services Pvt. Ltd. update its privacy policy?

We may update this policy at any time by posting additions or modifications on this web page. You should regularly view this policy for any changes. Any changes will be effective immediately upon the posting of revised policy on the XcellHost Cloud Services Pvt. Ltd. official website www.xcellhost.in.

### IX. What is the jurisdiction for Privacy Policy?

It is notified to all concerned, that they agree that the jurisdiction and venue for any legal proceedings relating to this policy shall be in appropriate courts at Mumbai, India and in accordance with the applicable laws of India.

### X. What is the severability for Privacy Policy?

If for any reason any provision herein is found void or unenforceable, it will stand severed to the extent unenforceable and the remaining provisions will continue in full force and effect.
